Module Room
Sun Wukong
Mojo-mojo-mojo spy
Mojo spy
This world is colorful and charming, truth and lies confuse our eyes.
Look with your heart and you'll see, the truth is never far away.
Hey you, good or bad, truth or lies, can't escape the smoke of the soul.
Take all your courage, maybe you can save this world.
Mojo Mojo Mojo Spy
Mojo Spy
In the previous episode...
Tuna Town's richest man, Ye Yongfu's daughter, vanished mysteriously.
To find his daughter,
He hired Jimmy Chen, Locky Qi, and Hawxing.
They investigated the castle.
In Princess Ye's room,
Locky Qi found a mysterious email from someone named Nintendough
On the computer.
The Real and Fake Princess
What happened?
Hawxing suddenly fainted with a thud while working just now.
Now I can only rely on you to find my daughter
Is Hawxing okay
He might have fainted from exhaustion
He's been sent to the guest room to rest
Heh heh, who told him to always grab the spotlight?
Karma, huh?
Locky Qi
Lord Ye
Don't worry
We've already found some clues
Really?
The Queen malfunctioned for only five minutes
And from the main door to Princess Ye's room
it takes at least seven minutes at best
Plus there are no signs of struggle in the room
The kidnapper couldn't possibly
have completed the kidnapping in such a short time
So then
there's only one possibility
Your daughter went out and got herself kidnapped
What?
That's impossible
Ye is always a good kid
We found an email on her computer that
she didn't have time to delete
It says here
Princess Ye was planning to run away from home all along.
And I bet
the Queen and all the Ye family robots got poisoned
because of her.
No way.
She doesn't have that kind of knowledge.
But the person who sent the email
is probably some virus expert.
If they teamed up with Princess Ye from the inside,
then the virus could easily break in.
Well... that's possible.
Little Ye may be well-behaved,
but she's always resented the Queen
having her mother's personality.
I should have had the Queen monitor her emails.
Monitor?
This isn't a prison, you know.
What did you say?
Nothing, nothing!
I mean, if there *was* monitoring,
this wouldn't have happened.
You... you're Locky Qi, right?
Can you find out where Ye went?
Now we've got an email address.
Let the queen review the email source through the server.
Then we'll know where that online friend is.
I think I found her.
Then we’ll have a clue to your daughter’s whereabouts.
Found it.
Mail from 69 Hailingtian, Tuna Town
A man named Nintendough.
So what are we waiting for?
Wait, Locky Qi.
We still don't know what Princess Ye looks like.
Please give us a photo for our investigation.
Hold on.
Coming, coming!
Is Nintendough at home?
I am. Who are you?
I'm private detective Jimmy Chen.
Entrusted by someone.
Coming to investigate.
Excuse me, do you know Princess Ye?
I don't know.
Really?
Why are there emails from you on Ye's computer?
You also wrote the virus in Ye's main computer, didn't you?
No, that's not it.
I didn't write a virus. The virus crashed the Queen system.
I never mentioned the Queen, you did.
Guilty conscience.
Spill it.
What else do you know?
I know she wanted to run away from home.
She asked me to find a computer whiz to make a virus.
Where is Princess Ye now?
I heard him mention Tuna Town Hotel.
She might be staying there.
I'm warning you—
If we don't find her, you're under arrest.
Sorry.
Miss Ye has already checked out.
Hey, is this Detective Jimmy Chen?
My daughter is back home already.
If it weren't for you,
my daughter wouldn't have come home safely.
What's going on?
Let me explain.
I planned this kidnapping myself.
The goal was to test if Dad still cared about me.
Then I found out from Nintendough
that he hired the best detective to search everywhere for me.
I got what I wanted.
just returned to my father's side
Such a strange idea
Ye
Father has been too strict with you before
It's all my fault
Please don't do this again
You're my only daughter
Huh? When did your hands get so rough?
From practicing the piano
You never paid attention
You only looked at the queen and missed Mother
I'm sorry
But you need to know
You and the queen, in my heart—
—are equally important
No, no
From today on
You are the most important
Since everything has been resolved
Then we'll take our leave
Please wait
You must stay
for a simple meal
And I heard Detective Hawxing say
your computer skills are also impressive
不敢当
有什么事需要我帮忙吗
是这样
霍侦探发现
主电脑中有病毒残留
但他现在身体不舒服
无法帮助皇后
所以想请你帮忙
难得见霍星会求人
我希望你能留下来
相信今晚会有一顿美味的大餐
失败者还这么嚣张
对不起
我先回房间休息了
切断和叶家局域网的联系
开始分析病毒
果然
陈侦探
没想到你这个小外甥这么厉害
真是英雄出少年
那当然
你这个笨蛋
这可是妈妈送给我的晚礼服
我
好了好了
Ye
Don't lose your cool.
Finally made it back.
Let's have a nice family reunion dinner!
Sorry.
I... I'll head to my room and rest.
It's so late.
What are you doing here?
I should be the one asking you that.
Miss Ye
What are you doing?
Mind your own business.
You're not Princess Ye at all.
Ye Chengzhu is blind in both eyes.
Can't recognize you.
You're using a virus too.
Destroy the queen's identification system.
And the calluses on your hands.
And definitely not from piano practice.
It's from practicing with your weapon on your waist, isn't it?
Say.
Who are you?
Why steal the statue?
Where's the real Princess Ye?
Hmph, that's fine.
I still prefer to be straightforward
I am Shaker
A senior executive of The Illumin-Eye
Smashing all obstacles in front of Dottie and me
Is the belief of my life
The Illumin-Eye again
Who is Dottie?
The leader of your organization?
Dottie
What's wrong?
Huh? What's this?
The one you brought back is just a thief
The real Princess Ye's whereabouts are still unknown
[Ending Theme]
Being alone, lonely and solitary
At that time, life
Is bound to have some unhappiness
Saying goodbye to today
Always makes people feel lost
Look at tomorrow
Waving to me on your horizon
Every day is just sunrise and sunset
Plunging into time, dreaming more
Anticipate in life
Every second, every moment
Bright eyes are sparkling
Smiling into the sunlight
Stepping through the bridge
At the heavy crossroads